const theme_Questions_Returns = [
  [
    { id: 1, title: "Track my return" },
    {
      id: 2,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "How can I track my return?",
      answer:
        "You can track your return with our Return Tracker or by clicking the 'Track your return' button located within the Return Request Confirmation email you received after creating your return on our website. * Note: return tracking is not available for all countries.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 3, title: "Returns" },
    {
      id: 4,
      idTitle: 3,
      question: "What is your return policy?",
      answer:
        "We gladly accept returns for a refund or exchange within 30 days of purchase. We even cover the cost of return shipping with a few exceptions noted below. Returns must be in new condition, and we ask that they are in their original packaging –including apparel and accessories",
    },

    {
      id: 5,
      idTitle: 3,
      question: "How can I return my order?",
      answer:
        "Just grab your order number and email used to place the order and submit our return or exchange form.",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      idTitle: 3,
      question: "What if i lost my pre paid label?",
      answer:
        "Please reach out to us through our Contact Us form. We're happy to help you with this.",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      idTitle: 3,
      question: "Do you offer free return shipping?",
      answer:
        "We do offer free return shipping for most countries, but not all. Free return shipping is not yet covered in India, Indonesia and Malaysia. If you have additional questions, please reach out to us.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 8, title: "Refunds" },
    {
      id: 9,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "I want return my itens for a refund.",
      answer:
        "Not a problem. If your items are eligible for return, we will refund the amount paid, including any tax, for the item returned once we receive and check in the return. Please note, a return request must be submitted to receive your refund. Eligible returns are within our 30-day return window and products are in new condition in their original, intact packaging. Expedited shipping costs will not be refunded for orders returned or exchanged.",
    },

    {
      id: 10,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "When will receive my refund?",
      answer:
        "Your refund will be issued after our warehouse team receives your return and can check in and verify the items. We appreciate your patience while we work to process your return.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 11, title: "Exchanges" },
    {
      id: 12,
      idTitle: 11,
      question:
        "what is the process for exchaging a order for a different size?",
      answer:
        "Begin your exchange via our return and exchange form, then send the original item back to us via the shipping label provided to you. Once we receive the original item and the warehouse checks the item in, your new size will be processed for shipping. An email is sent when the exchange size ships with tracking information.",
    },

    {
      id: 13,
      idTitle: 11,
      question: "Can I exchange my order for a different color?",
      answer:
        "We're unable to process exchanges for different colors. In this case, please simply return your original order and place a new order for the color you desire.",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      idTitle: 11,
      question: "Can I exchange an exchange?",
      answer:
        "We aren’t able to exchange any exchange orders at this time. To proceed, please return your exchange by reaching out to us on our contact us form and then place a new order on our website.",
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      idTitle: 11,
      question: "Can I get a refund for a exchange?",
      answer:
        "Yes, we accept returns for exchanged items if it is within 30 days of receiving the product and the products are in new condition. Our return and exchange form doesn't allow us to process returns on exchanges, so please reach out to the Happiness Delivery Team through our Contact Us form.",
    },
  ],
];

export default theme_Questions_Returns;
